

# JORDAN LENABURG

Jordan.Lenaburg@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/iordanlenabura



github.com/iordanlenaburg



**A**BOUT

Full Stack JS Web Developer – 6+ years building and servicing internal web apps – Designed and authored simple JS web apps for process standardization and efficiency – Initially self-taught and later sought formal education

_			
5	KI	Ш	١ς

JAVASCRIPT	REACT JS
JQuery	Node JS
Angular JS	Express JS
HTML/CSS	MS Visual Studio

COACHING RECENT PROJECTS

MP3-Downloader SPA interacting with multiple API's to search YouTube and download the audio,

CRUD application interacting with a simple to-do database through API. Designed to be responsive using bootstrap.

Angular To Do

Static application which displays a list of high-scores for user submitted games. Responsive without bootstrap.

HIGH SCORE

MongoDB MS EXCEL PROJECT MANAGEMENT

also displaying lyrics and metadata. Technologies Used: AngularJS, Bootstrap, CSS3, HTML5

Technologies Used: AngularJS, Bootstrap, CSS3, HTML5

Technologies Used: jQuery, CSS3, HTML5, Session web storage

#### EXPERIENCE

**Client Services Supervisor** 

JAN 2014 - MAY 2017 84401 OGDEN, UT **F**SURANCE

- •Designed and created JavaScript web app for standardizing customer service noting procedures
- •Established call center operations: performance incentives, coaching strategies, normalized procedures
- Designed and implemented JavaScript application for underwriting agents to note investigation results

#### **Internet Sales Associate**

May 2013 - Nov 2013 TIM DAHLE IMPORTS 84107 Murray, UT

- Created lead follow-up process for "Archived Leads"
- Executed new "10 Step" sales training process
- Piloted Virtual Product Presentation lead response initiative

## **Customer Service Associate 3**

84020 DRAPER, UT Jun 2008 - Dec 2012

- •Inherited and adapted vanilla JavaScript web app for standardizing format for account notes
- •Self-Taught JavaScript and created input validation web app to standardize procedures for customer refund initiative
- •Ranked 99th percentile of agent performance year over year

## **Quality Assurance Lead**

BYDEX MANAGEMENT 84116 SALT LAKE CITY, UT JAN 2007 - APR 2008

- •Spawned new QA definition criteria for sales and customer service agents
- Designed and implemented Monthly Subscription call flow process for quality evaluation and grading
- Upgraded existing call flow processes and evaluated effectiveness for sales and service organization

### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack JavaScript Web **Development** V SCHOOL April 2017- Jul 14 2017

**Bachelor of Science Business IT** Management

WESTERN GOVERNORS UNIVERSITY FEB 2015 - JUL 2017

**Project+ Project Management** Certification

COMPTIA May 2016